flexshopper.com 2016-06-10

# Rent to own Computers, Electronics, Appliances, Furniture - FlexShopper

**Privacy Policy Statement** effective 11/27/2013 ****

This privacy policy describes how FlexShopper LLC. (“we” or “us”) collects, uses and shares information about that is captured while you use this website.

NOTE: We do not sell our products to anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, **do not** register on our site.

**Your Consent**  
By accessing or using Flexshopper.com (the “site”) or by leasing or applying to lease a product through FlexShopper, you consent to the privacy practices

**How Do We Collect Information And What Information Do We Collect?**  
We may collect information from you including, but not limited to, when you: lease or rent any products; order, return or exchange products; contact us through our site or using a social media platform such as Facebook; sign up for emails, mobile messages or social media notifications from us; enter a contest or sweepstakes on our site; or provide comments, suggestions or other input. We may collect personal information such as your name, social security number, email address, home or work address, or telephone number(s). We may also collect demographic information such as your ZIP code, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites for business purposes including, but not limited to, developing a better understanding of our customers and improving our offerings.  
We also collect certain non-personal, anonymous information about your use of our sites as well about your computer, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. We use this information for our general business operations, to maintain the quality of our services, and to provide general statistics regarding our customers’ use of the site. Except as otherwise explained in this policy, we may combine the non-personal information we collect from you with your personal information.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technology**   
Our website also uses "cookies" (small data files stored on your computer) and other tracking technologies to collect information about your visit to our sites. The cookies and tracking technologies we use do not capture personally-identifiable information. The information that is captured about your visit may be used in a variety of ways, such as to monitor and maintain information about your visits to our website, to help us identify and address problems with and to improve our website, to analyze web traffic trends, and to help protect the security and integrity of our website. You may set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you receive cookies, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies however, you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

We may also use pixel tags (also known as “clear gifs,” “Web beacons” or “1-by-1gifs”). These may be used in connection with certain pages of our sites or with email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, and to assist us in resolving issues that may arise on this website.

**How We Use Collected Personally-Identifiable Information**

We may use the personally-identifiable information we collect for the following purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries, fulfill your requests, process transactions, and facilitate collecting payments;
  * to communicate to you important information regarding this website, changes to our Terms and Conditions, and/or other administrative information;
  * for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our sites, improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * for risk control, to comply with laws and regulations and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements;
  * _if you register a profile with us_ , to contact you, via the phone or email:
    * to update you on the status of your order and for related product or service information; and
    * for marketing purposes, such as notifying you of product discounts, website changes, company news, and promotions;
    * to conduct surveys and research regarding your opinion of our current services or potential new services that we may offer; and
  * to personalize your experience or to improve our website and website offerings by allowing us to customize the content and/or layout of our page based on feedback and information we receive from you.

We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information is not transferred to a third party.

**How Do We Protect Your Personal Information?**  
We implement a variety of industry standard security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information, including encryption technologies. When you provide us with certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect you to a secure server. At our actual facilities we implement security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at this website. Unfortunately, no security technology is completely secure, and you should remember that email is not a secure means of communication.

**Do We Disclose Your Personal Information To Outside Parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties without your consent. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, processing transactions, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as these parties agree to keep this information confidential, consistent with this privacy policy. We also may disclose this information to third parties: (1) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of this website, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; or (2) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process. We may report information about your account to credit bureaus. Late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account may be reflected in your credit report. Non-personal information collected at this website may be provided to third-parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
Vermont residents: We will not disclose information about you with affiliates or non-affiliated, third party companies or financial institutions, other than as required or permitted by law, without your express permission.  
California residents: We will not share information we collect about you with affiliated or non-affiliated third parties, except in the limited circumstances permitted under state law, or if you give us your permission.  
Nevada residents: If you would like more information regarding this notice or Nevada’s law regarding corporate do-not-call registries, you can contact us at the toll-free number or address included in this notice or the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General at 555 E. Washington Street, Suite 3900, Las Vegas, Nevada 89101; Phone: (702)486-3132/Email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.  
North Dakota residents: We will not disclose information about you with non-affiliated, third party companies or financial institutions, other than as required or permitted by law, without your express permission.

**How Do You Stop Receiving Marketing And Other Communications?**  
As mentioned, most browsers can be configured to reject cookies or other tracking technologies or alert you when cookies are being placed on your computer. If you would like to stop receiving communications from us or to cancel your profile, log into your account, go to the Change Account Preferences page and select your information sharing and contact preferences. If you would like to cease receiving marketing emails from us, just click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email and you will shortly cease receiving emails from us. By electing to opt-out of information sharing, you will not receive updates on new products, services, or special offers.

**Third Party Links**  
This website may contain links to other websites so that you may learn more about the products available through us and other matters that we feel may be of interest to you. We are providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by us of the site or any association with its operators. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those websites, and are in no manner responsible or liable for the availability and content of the websites to which this website is linked. We make no representations whatsoever about any other site you may access through this website. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them. Any concerns regarding any product or service offered by a website to which this website is linked or the link itself should be directed to the operator of that specific website and not to us.

**Google Analytics Remarketing**  
This website uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Double Click cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

**Collection and Use of Bank Account Information**  
As part of our information collection process, we may detect additional bank accounts under the ownership of the consumer. We will consider these additional accounts to be part of the application process. By applying, you authorize us to search for and evaluate bank accounts under your ownership for this purpose.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**  
We respect the privacy of your children, and we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We do not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information from consumers under the age of thirteen (13). You must be at least eighteen (18) years of age to obtain services from us.

**Limited to Online Privacy Policy**  
This online privacy policy applies to information collected through our website only, and not to information collected offline.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy at any time in the future. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this web page with the date of revision. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.

**Contact Information**  
We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Policy Statement. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us at legal@FlexShopper.com.
